Indiana University President Emeritus John W. Ryan papers, 1944-2011 C456
Indiana University Archives
- Office files, 1944-2011 (Box 1)
  - Pac Rim Group Co., LTD. (Potential consulting assignment as higher education institutional specialist with ADB Lao DPR Project), 1995 (Box 8)
  - Perlman, Daniel W., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Philanthropy, Center on, 2007 (Box 8)
  - Phillips, Harvey, 1994-2001 (Box 8)
  - Polish Studies Center, 1988-2010 (Box 8)
  - Political Science (Department of) and 75th Anniversary Celebration (John W. Ryan Speaker), October 20-21, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Portrait--John W. Ryan, 1988 (Box 8)
  - President's Office (Indiana University) (Box 8)
    - Michael A. McRobbie (Box 8)
      - General, 2007-2010 (Box 8)
      - Inauguration of Michael McRobbie, October 18, 2007 (Box 8)
      - General, 2011 (Box 8)
    - Adam Herbert (Box 8)
      - General, 2003-2007 (Box 8)
      - Inauguration of Adam Herbert Thursday, April 15, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Myles Brand (Box 8)
      - General, 1993-2004 (Box 8)
      - Inauguration Of Myles Brand, January 19, 1995 (Box 8)
      - Inaugural Symposium "The Future of the Public University in the Twenty First Century" (John W. Ryan Moderator), January 18, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Tom Ehrlich (Box 8)
      - General, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
      - Briefing Papers on Presidents Ehrlich's Trip to Asia, June 27- July 8, 1993 (Box 8)
      - Inauguration of President Ehlrich, October 11-12, 1987 (Box 8)
  - President's Office, John W. Ryan's Professional Activities Update, 1987-1994 (Box 8)
  - President's Office, "We are One University with Eight Front Doors", 1989-1993 (Box 8)
  - Purdue University, 1990-2007 (Box 8)
  - Q, 1995-2005 (Box 8)
  - R, 1987-2001 (Box 8)
  - Randolph-Macon College Commencement (John W. Ryan speaker), June 1, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Recommendations (Box 8)
    Conditions Governing Access
    (RESTRICTED)
    - 2010 (Box 8)
    - 2005-2009 (Box 8)
    - 1995-2005 (Box 8)
    - 1994 (Box 8)
    - 1993 (Box 8)
    - 1992 (Box 8)
    - 1991 (Box 8)
    - Letters of A-F, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
    - Letters of G-Z, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
    - Student, 1992-2001 (Box 8)
  - Regional Campuses (Box 8)
    - IU EAST General File, 1995-2005 (Box 8)
    - IUPU At Fort Wayne General File, 1994 (Box 8)
    - IUPUI (Box 8)
      - General File, 1989-2003 (Box 8)
      - Campus Campaign, 2000-2002 (Box 8)
      - 20th Anniversary Symposium: "The Urban University in the 21st Century" The Urban University in an International Theme- John W. Ryan Speaker, November 8, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Dean of the Faculties, 1993-1997 (Box 8)
      - "History & Development of the Health Sciences," Luncheon meeting, October 29, 2003 (Box 8)
      - Wells Scholar Program, February, 19, 1991 (Box 8)
      - International Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
      - Medicine, (School of) (Box 8)
        - General, 2008-2011 (Box 8)
        - Urology, 2000 (Box 8)
        - Capital Campaign Public Announcement Celebration-Lilly Corp., October 28, 1993 (Box 8)
      - Oral History Project sponsored by the Senior Academy of IUPUI, 1997 (Box 8)
      - Purdue School of Engineering & Technoloy – 30th Anniversary Celebration, 2002 (Box 8)
      - Center on Southeast Asia (Box 8)
        - General File, 1995-1997 (Box 8)
        - John W. Ryan: First Senior Fellow of the Center on Southeast Asia IUPUI Office, 1995 (Box 8)
        - Senios Academy, 1993-2003 (Box 8)
        - Thailand, 1995 (Box 8)
        - Vietnam, 1995 (Box 8)
        - Steering communities, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
      - Southeast Asia Study Committee General File, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - Southeast Asia Study Committee General File, 1991 (Box 9)
    - IU Kokomo General File, 1990-2009 (Box 9)
    - IU Northwest (Box 9)
      - General File, 1999-2010 (Box 9)
      - Patricia & John W. Ryan Fund, 1998-2001 (Box 9)
      - World Affairs Council of Northwest IN, 1988-1991 (Box 9)
    - IU South Bend General File, 1989-2009 (Box 9)
    - IU Southeast General File, 1995 (Box 9)
  - The Remnant Trust (Box 9)
    - 2009-2010 (Box 9)
    - Bex, Brian The Remnant Trust (American Communication Network), 2003-2009 (Box 9)
    - The Remnant Trust letters, 2006 (Box 9)
    - Bex: The Remnant Trust Jeffersonville Carnegie, 2005-2009 (Box 9)
    - The Remnant Trust/ IUF Wed. @ 5:30pm Jeffersonville, IN, September 26, 2007 (Box 9)
    - Remnant Trust- June 8 & 9 2005 Brooking, SD, June 11 & 12, 2005 (Box 9)
    - Remnant Trust Board Meeting & Display- University Club in NY, September, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Reviews: National Endowment for the Humanities, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Rotary Club Scholarship, Speak at Banquet Madison, IN, May 12, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Reception Honoring D. Patricia Ryan 1993 DASA Recipient 3:00-5:00 pm Sunday 3:00-5:00 pm, June 20, 1993 (Box 9)
  - John W. Ryan (Box 9)
    - Fellows Program- SPEA October, 2006 (Box 9)
    - Honorary Degree South Dakota State University, June 11, 2005 (Box 9)
    - Interviews, 1997-2008 (Box 9)
    - International Education (SUNY The John W. Ryan Fellowship), December, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Notes (Get Well), 2007-2010 (Box 9)
    - Surgery (Box 9)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 9)
      - June 5, 2001 (Box 9)
      - Notes of Concern Following Surgery, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Ryan, John W. Award (Given at Founders Day for exceptional contributions to international programs at IU) (Box 9)
    - University Medal, September 2009 (Box 9)
  - S, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Salzburg Seminar (See Foreign Travel), 2006 (Box 9)
  - Schilt, Alexander F., 1995 (Box 9)
  - Sease, Gerig and Wilcox file: Taylor International, 1989-1992 (Box 9)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon: Scholarship Awards Dinner Saturday, (John W. Ryan speaker), September 6, 2008 (Box 9)
  - Singapore International Foundation, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Indiana Association of Cities & Town/ IN Sister City Fort Wayne, IN, September, 21 & 22, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Public and Environmental Affairs, School of (SPEA) (Box 9)
    - General Information/ Memos, 2010 (Box 9)
    - Copy of the original proposal to establish SPEA, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Office of the Dean, 2000-2011 (Box 9)
    - Bonser Retirement Colloquium and Dinner Thursday, April 24, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Dean's Council Meeting binders (Box 9)
      - April 14-15 2011 (Box 9)
      - September 16-17 2010 (Box 9)
      - May 18-19 2010 (Box 9)
      - June 2011 (Box 10)
    - Board of Visitors (Box 10)
      - September 25-26, 2008 (Box 10)
      - 2003-2008 (Box 10)
    - Development, Susan Johnson-IUB, Denise Wagner IUPUI, 1998-2008 (Box 10)
    - Development Committees, Montgomery, Glen & Bonser, Chuck- MTGS, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Globalization of SPEA (Ad Hoc group), 2001 (Box 10)
    - Ruckelshaus Speech, April 19, 2009 (Box 10)
    - Rutledge (Phillip) Fellows Program, 2003-2007 (Box 10)
    - Rutledge, Phil - "Deans I have Known", 2007 (Box 10)
    - Strategic Plan Vision Statement, 1998-2002 (Box 10)
    - 25th Anniversary, 1997 (Box 10)
  - St. John Church Sesquicentennial (John W. Ryan speaker) Sunday, November 8, 1987 (Box 10)
  - State Fair, August 7, 2008 (Box 10)
  - Donald C. Stone - Luncheon, April 15,1993 (Box 10)
  - Stoner, Richard B., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Student Admission, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Student Problems, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Study of the President, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Summa Liberte, Brian Bex. John W. Ryan contributor. (Box 10)
    Arrangement
    Filed at end of collection (See Box 23)
  - Sympathy Notes (Box 10)
    - 2000-2011 (Box 10)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 10)
  - T, 1994-2009 (Box 10)
  - Taylor International (Paul Tarnoff): Sease, Gerig & Wilcox, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Tenri University Japan, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Museum Catalog (Box 10)
  - Texas Tech University (Box 10)
    - General, 2001-2008 (Box 10)
    - Commencement and, December 13-15, 2002; May 11, 2007 (Box 10)
  - Thailand (Box 10)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 1992-2011 (Box 10)
    - Dinner honoring Thai Visitors (Dentistry), May 8, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Report on Mission to Bangkok in Relation to Proposed Indiana-Thammasat Public Administration Contract, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Thank you letters, 1988-2008 (Box 10)
  - Thorson, Thomas L., 1995-1996 (Box 10)
  - Tobias, Randall L., 1992-2007 (Box 10)
  - Tow, Ted C., (Former Associate Executive Director at NCAA), 1944 (Box 10)
  - Tribute, Letters of, 1992-2002 (Box 10)
  - Trustees, Board of (Indiana University), 1989-2002 (Box 10)
  - Ulmer, John - Presentation of the Sagamore of the Wabash, May 25, 1988 (Box 10)
  - United Aram Emirates University (Box 10)
    - General, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Search Couseuet., 1990 (Box 10)
    - United Arab Emirates Report and Review, May 1989 (Box 10)
    - Report of the External Examinters of the Faculty of Economics and Administrative Sciences, July 1990 (Box 11)
    - United Arab Emirates, September 15-24, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Report of Examiner to the University of United Arab Emirate-School of Economics & Administrative Science with special Reference to Dept. of Political Science, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Report of External Examiners, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Faculty of Administrative & Political Sciences (FAPS) (Box 11)
  - Unidentified audio tapes, undated (Box 17)
  - US Department of Education-Standards to Promote Drug Free Colleges and Universities (Vonnie Veltri), 1986-1988 (Box 11)
  - University Field Staff International, 1999 (Box 11)
  - University Faculty Club in Indianapolis, INC., 1988 (Box 11)
  - University of Maryland (Box 11)
    - The Maryland School of Public Affairs, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Baltimore (Box 11)
      - General, 1994-1996 (Box 11)
      - Interim President, Jan. 3, 1994-May 20, 1994 (Box 11)
      - School of Pharmacy, 1994-1996 (Box 11)
  - University of Massachusetts (Box 11)
    - General File, 2005 (Box 11)
    - Commission on the Future of the University (Box 11)
      - General File, 1989-1994 (Box 11)
      - Meeting, February 23, 1989 (Box 11)
      - Meeting, February 2, 1989 (Box 11)
      - Meeting, December 10, 1988 (Box 11)
      - Meeting, October 28, 1988 (Box 11)
      - Meeting, September 30, 1988 (Box 11)
      - Meeting, April 25, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Administrators of the 1960s & 1970s reunion, April 10 & 11, 1995 (Box 11)
  - University of Texas at Tyler (Box 11)
    - General, April 27, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Strategic Plan, 1989-1995 (Box 11)
  - Urban League Dinner (Box 11)
    - December 12, 1988 (Box 11)
    - December 12, 1988 (Box 11)
  - US Kraine (Nadia McConnell), 2004-2006 (Box 11)
  - V, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Vice President Bloomington, 1990-2005 (Box 11)
  - Vice President & Chief Financial Officer (Judith G. Palmer), 1998-2006 (Box 11)
  - Vice President Facilities, 1988-1995 (Box 11)
  - Vice President for Public Affairs and Government Relations, 1996-1999 (Box 11)
  - Vice President- Regional Campuses, 2010 (Box 11)
  - Vice President for Student Development and Diversity, 2007 (Box 11)
  - Vice President for University Relations: Impact Statement, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Virginia Fundraising Institute - Sponsored by the Shenandoah chapter of the National Society of Fund Raising Executives (John W. Ryan Keynote Speaker), May 20, 1993 (Box 11)
  - W, 1988-2001 (Box 12)
  - Walther Cancer Institute, 1999-2005 (Box 12)
  - Washington, G. Gregory, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Walter Washington Roast - Annual Scholarship Roast, Tougaloo College, September 11, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Washington University, September 7, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Wells, Herman B (Box 12)
    - University Chancellor, 1998-2000 (Box 12)
    - Biography Project (J. Capshew), 2005-2009 (Box 12)
    - Visionaries Awards, 2000 (Box 12)
    - University Chancellor, 1994-2000 (Box 12)
    - Obituary file, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Wentworth, Jack - Recognition Ceremony, May 21, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Willbern, York, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Wilkie, Wendell - Centennial Symposium Celebration, February 15-17, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Williams, Edgar G., 2004 (Box 12)
  - Wise, Charles & Wise, Lois, 1992-2003 (Box 12)
  - Wolfson, Les, 1993-2003 (Box 12)
  - Woodland Campus, The, 2009 (Box 12)
  - X (Box 12)
  - Y (Box 12)
  - Young, Charles E. (Sue) Chancellor - UCLA President University of FL, 1994-2006 (Box 12)
  - Z (Box 12)
- Speeches, 1988-2000 (Box 12)
  - 26 September, 1987 (Box 12)
  - 8 November, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Award Ceremony, Commander, Order of Merit of the Polish People's Republic Indianapolis, Indiana, 23 March, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Rotary Scholarship Banquet, Madison Indiana, 12 May, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Canterbury School Commencement Address Fort Wayne, Indiana, 10 June, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Huber H. Humphrey Award, 84th Annual Meeting, American Political Science Association Washington, D.C., 1-4 September, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Huntington College Foundation Banquet Huntington, Indiana, 8 September, 1988 (Box 12)
  - Keynote Speaker, First Annual meeting of Indiana Sister Cities, Inc. Fort Wayne, Indiana, 22 September, 1988 (Box 12)
  - 43rd Annual Dinner, Urban League of Northwest Indiana. Gary, Indiana, 12 December, 1988 (Box 12)
  - "Tyler's World" (notes on Address), The University of Texas at Tyler, Tyler Texas., 27 April, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Angola High School's Annual Academic Excellence Recognition Program Angola, Indiana, 22 May, 1989 (Box 12)
  - The Henry Ferrettie Memorial, Inc., Fourth Annual Recognition Dinner and Award Ceremony, South Bend, Indiana, 5 October, 1989 (Box 12)
  - American Cancer Society University (Speech Notes) 15th Annual Leadership Development Conference, Brown County State Park Nashville, Indiana, 3 June, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Retirement Dinner Honoring Dr. Richard G. Landini, President, Indiana State University Terre Haute, Indiana, 12 June, 1992 (Box 12)
  - "U" In the World, NASULGC Commission on International Affairs, Washington, D.C., 14 June, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Alabama Power Company, Industrial Interchange Executive Conference, Marriot's Grand Hotel at Point Clear, Alabama, 14, July, 1992 (Box 12)
  - "The International Role of Metropolitan Universities" Metropolitan Universities (International), December 1992 (Box 12)
  - Remarks delivered to the Plenary Session of the Hungarian Accreditation Committee Budapest, Hungary, 1 March, 1993 (Box 12)
  - International Association of Universities, University of Coimbra (Portugal)/University of Salamanca (Spain) Seminar Remarks: Response to the European Challenge, 19-24 April, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Remarks: International Council Dinner, Federal Room, Indiana Memorial Union, Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana, 17 May, 1993 (Box 12)
  - "Mission of Philanthropy" Shenandoah Chapter, National Society of Fund Raising Executives Charlottesville, Virginia, 20 May, 1993 (Box 12)
  - "Presidents Commission Turns 10" NCAA News Supplement, Special 88th convention issue, 5 January, 1994 (Box 12)
  - "Resource Allocation Systems Inside Universities" Université de Bourgogne, Dijon France, 24-26 March, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Opening Ceremony: IUPUI/Tenga Nasional Berhad Project New Engineering Program in Bangi, Malaysia, 11 July, 1994 (Box 12)
  - IMHE Conference on Institutional Strategies for Internationalization, 10 October, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Celebration of the 75th Anniversary of the Founding of Nankai University, Nankai University, Tianjin, Peoples Republic of China, October, 16 1994 (Box 12)
  - Kappa Sigma 60th Biennial Grand Conclave Richmond, Virginia, July, 20 1995 (Box 12)
  - Retirement of Dean Walter Daly, Indianapolis, Indiana, October 31, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Chief Advancement Officers Meeting, Fashion Institute of Technology-SUNY, September 11, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Operation Information Workshops for School Counselors, Maritime College, Fort Schuyler, New York-SUNY, September 18, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Business Officers Association (SUBOA)- State University of New York, September 19, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Operation Information Workshop for School Counselors, Alfred State College, Alfred, New York--SUNY, September 27, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Senate Meeting, State University of New York, September 28, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Convocation, State University of New York at Buffalo, Buffalo, New York--SUNY, October 2, 1996 (Box 12)
  - College of Agriculture and Technology at Morrisville, Alfred, New York--SUNY, October 9, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Operation Information Workshop for School Counselors, College of Agriculture and Technology at Morrisville, Alfred, New York--SUNY, October 10, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Council of Community Colleges, Orange Community College--SUNY, October 19, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Student Assembly Leadership Conference, Utica, New York--SUNY, November 2, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Operation Information Workshops for school Counselors, Hudson Valley Community College, Rensselaer, New York--SUNY, November 4, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Inaugural Dinner, State University of New York at Albany, November 7, 1996 (Box 12)
  - SUNY Alumni Conference, Marriott Hotel, Albany, New York, November 8, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy, Annual Alumni Awards Dinner, State University of New York at Albany, December 2, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Talking Points-State University board of Trustee Meeting, State University Plazea Albany, New York, December 17, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Salzburg Seminar, Salzburg Austria-SUNY, January 23, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Memorial Gathering Remembering David R. Derge Carbondale, Illinois, March 22, 1997 (Box 12)
  - HVCC Inauguration of Stephen M. Curtis, Hudson Valley Community College--SUNY, April 4, 1997 (Box 12)
  - College of Human Ecology Advisory Council, State university of New York, April 18, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Address to the State University Community, new York Network Broadcast--SUNY, April 25, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Centennial Symposium, Hangzhou University, People's Republic of China--SUNY, May 3, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Commencement Address, Institute of Technology at Utica/Rome, State university of New York, May 17, 1997 (Box 12)
  - College of Optometry Commencement, State university of New York, May 18, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Commencement Address, Broome Community College--SUNY, May 23, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Albany Bicentenary Ceremony, State University Plaza, Albany, New York--SUNY, May 28, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Randolph-Macon College Commencement, Ashland Virginia, June 1, 1997 (Box 12)
  - SUNY Mayor's Coalition, June 23, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Conference Celebrating the 40th Anniversary of Title VI of the Higher Education Act, Washington, D.C., April 17, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Capital Rescue Mission Ceremony, State university of New York, December 17, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Funeral Remarks-Claude Rich, February 13, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Globalization and the Local University, August 1999 (Box 12)
  - Alliance of Distinguished Rank and Named Professors, Indiana University, Bloomington Indiana, November 16, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, College of Optometry, State university of New York, December 14, 1999 (Box 12)
  - A Celebration of a Life: Remembering Herman B Wells, Indiana University Auditorium, Bloomington Indiana, April 5, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Tribute to Dr. and Mrs. Steven C. Beering, Purdue University, May 1, 2000 (Box 12)
  - The Transatlantic Consortium for Public Policy Analysis and Education Colloquium, Globalization and Regionalization: A Paradoxical Challenge for Public Policy, Maastrict, The Netherlands, May 22-25, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Globalization of Higher Education, Economics of Higher Education: Efficiency-equity-ethics, Istanbul, Turkey, October 12, 2000 (Box 12)
  - A Life Celebrated: Dr. Joseph Thomas Taylor (Outline), October 23, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Memories of Sue Young, October 2001 (Box 12)
  - Universities Project – Visiting Advisors Program, A Report of Consultation on "The Role of the University in the Emerging Civil Society" Adam Mickiewicz University, Poznan, Poland, February 18-22, 2002 (Box 12)
  - The Interim President: Effective Leadership Transition - Report to Thomas H. Langevin and Associates, June 2002 (Box 12)
  - Wells Gathering – IU Foundation Employee of the Month - Herman B Wells: Hoosier Mentor, August 9, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Commencement Address to Texas Tech University Ceremonies, December 14, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Inauguration of John V. Lombardi - Chancellor University of Massachusetts-Amherst, February 7, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Visit to Florida International University - (President Modesto Maidique), Miami, FL., August 30-Sept. 1, 2004 (Box 12)
  - International Conference in honor of the 250th Anniversary of Moscow State University, January 24, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Why SPEA? SPEA Board of Visitors, April 20, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Cream and Crimson Alumni Weekend - DASA Ceremony: Ronald Webb, June 17, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Mass of Christian Burial - The Honorable John M. Ryan Indianapolis, IN, July 12, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Kappa Sigma Scholarship Leadership Conference, Salt Lake City, UT, July 28-30, 2006 (Box 12)
  - International Role of the University - Izmir, Turkey, September 2006 (Box 12)
  - Ryan Fellows Program at SPEA - IU Auditorium, Bloomington, IN, October 26, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Russian/American Studies Center Anniversary Celebration - Moscow State University, October 31, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Kappa Sigma - Toast to Jim Payne. Hattiesburg, MS, October 6, 2007 (Box 12)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon Scholarship Banquet, Tudor Room, IMU, Bloomington, IN, September 6, 2008 (Box 12)
  - Introduction of Mark Kruzan - IU Retired Faculty/Staff Luncheon Bloomington, IN, September 10, 2008 (Box 12)
  - DASA Introduction of The Honorable Birch E. Bayh, Jr. - DASA Awards Dinner and Ceremony Alumni Hall, IMU, Bloomington, IN, June 20, 2009 (Box 12)
- Correspondence files, 1988-2011 (Box 12)
  - Alpha Copies, 1988-2011 (Box 12)
    - A (Box 12)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 12)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 12)
    - B (Box 12)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 12)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 12)
    - C (Box 12)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 12)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 12)
    - D (Box 12)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 12)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 12)
    - E (Box 12)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 12)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 12)
    - F (Box 12)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 12)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 12)
    - G (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - H (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - I (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - J (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - K (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - L (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - M (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - N (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - O (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - P (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
    - P-Q (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - Q (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
    - R (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - S (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - T (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - U (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
    - U-V (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - V (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
    - W (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 13)
    - X (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
    - Y (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
    - Y-Z (Box 13)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 13)
    - Z (Box 13)